<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version='2.0' xmlns:atom='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom'>
<channel>
<title>Nompower</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/</link>
<description>Daily digest</description>
<lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 03:41:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
<item>
<title>The Chan Zuckerberg Initiative cut 70 jobs as the Meta CEO’s philanthropy goes all in on mission to ‘cure or prevent all disease’</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-02-02-the-chan-zuckerberg-initiative-cut-70-jobs-as-the-meta-ceos-philanthropy-goes-al.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-02-02-the-chan-zuckerberg-initiative-cut-70-jobs-as-the-meta-ceos-philanthropy-goes-al.html</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 03:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
<description>In a move that signals a sharp strategic pivot, Mark Zuckerberg&#x27;s philanthropic arm is making deep cuts to its workforce to double down on a single, monumental goal. What Happened at the Chan Zuckerberg Initiative? The Chan Zuckerberg Initi</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Upcoming iPhone: A &quot;Flip&quot; Phone With a Square Foldable Design, Details Leaked</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-02-02-upcoming-iphone-a-flip-phone-with-a-square-foldable-design-details-leaked.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-02-02-upcoming-iphone-a-flip-phone-with-a-square-foldable-design-details-leaked.html</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 01:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
<description>The smartphone world is buzzing with a wild new rumor: Apple might be working on a foldable iPhone that flips shut like a classic clamshell, but with a distinctly modern, square profile. The Leaked Details According to a recent leak sourced</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Amazon’s ‘Melania’ documentary makes $7M on opening weekend</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-02-01-amazons-melania-documentary-makes-7m-on-opening-weekend.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-02-01-amazons-melania-documentary-makes-7m-on-opening-weekend.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 23:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
<description>In a quiet weekend for new theatrical releases, a documentary about a famously private figure has quietly posted a surprisingly strong box office number. The Numbers Behind the Headlines According to industry reports, &quot;Melania,&quot; a new docum</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Motorola is getting away with zero OS updates thanks to regulatory loophole | Motorola&#x27;s recent budget phones in Europe don&#x27;t offer any Android OS upgrades, but how?</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-02-01-motorola-is-getting-away-with-zero-os-updates-thanks-to-regulatory-loophole-moto.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-02-01-motorola-is-getting-away-with-zero-os-updates-thanks-to-regulatory-loophole-moto.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 23:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
<description>In the budget smartphone market, a new and troubling pattern is emerging that leaves buyers with a device frozen in time on day one. The Update Exemption Recent reports focus on specific Motorola budget models released in Europe, such as th</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Gear News of the Week: Samsung’s TriFold Sells Out in Minutes, and a Leak Teases Google’s New OS</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-02-01-gear-news-of-the-week-samsungs-trifold-sells-out-in-minutes-and-a-leak-teases-go.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-02-01-gear-news-of-the-week-samsungs-trifold-sells-out-in-minutes-and-a-leak-teases-go.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 19:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
<description>If you blinked this week, you might have missed the future of folding phones and the next potential shift in how our devices talk to each other. The tech rumor mill didn&#x27;t just churn; it went into overdrive, delivering two stories that have</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>B.C. teacher suspended for screening graphic film of industrial accident</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-02-01-b-c-teacher-suspended-for-screening-graphic-film-of-industrial-accident.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-02-01-b-c-teacher-suspended-for-screening-graphic-film-of-industrial-accident.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 19:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
<description>In an era where digital content is at our fingertips, a single classroom decision has ignited a firestorm over safety, education, and the raw power of unfiltered media. The Incident: A Classroom Lesson Goes Horribly Wrong According to repor</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple to launch M5 Pro, M5 Max MacBook Pros with macOS 26.3</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-02-01-apple-to-launch-m5-pro-m5-max-macbook-pros-with-macos-26-3.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-02-01-apple-to-launch-m5-pro-m5-max-macbook-pros-with-macos-26-3.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 18:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
<description>Hold onto your MagSafe cables, because the rumor mill is churning out a fresh batch of silicon-scented hype. A new whisper from the tech grapevine suggests Apple&#x27;s next seismic shift in personal computing is just over the horizon, and it&#x27;s </description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Nearly 70% of Lithuanian teachers use AI at work, prompting new guidelines</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-02-01-nearly-70-of-lithuanian-teachers-use-ai-at-work-prompting-new-guidelines.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-02-01-nearly-70-of-lithuanian-teachers-use-ai-at-work-prompting-new-guidelines.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 18:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
<description>While many education systems are still cautiously dipping their toes into the AI pool, Lithuania appears to be diving in headfirst. A quiet revolution is happening in its classrooms, and it&#x27;s being led by the teachers themselves. The Data-D</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>AI-supported breast cancer screening identified more women with clinically relevant cancers during the screening without a higher rate of false positives</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-02-01-ai-supported-breast-cancer-screening-identified-more-women-with-clinically-relev.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-02-01-ai-supported-breast-cancer-screening-identified-more-women-with-clinically-relev.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 17:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
<description>Imagine a world where your mammogram is read by a tireless, hyper-focused second set of eyes that never gets tired, never has an off day, and is trained on millions of previous scans. That future isn&#x27;t just coming—it&#x27;s starting to deliver o</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>What If the Sensors on Your Car Were Inspecting Potholes for the Government? Honda Found Out</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-02-01-what-if-the-sensors-on-your-car-were-inspecting-potholes-for-the-government-hond.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-02-01-what-if-the-sensors-on-your-car-were-inspecting-potholes-for-the-government-hond.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
<description>Imagine your daily commute, a chore you endure while sipping lukewarm coffee, is secretly a high-tech survey mission. The very sensors keeping you in your lane might be quietly cataloging the world&#x27;s crumbling infrastructure, turning your c</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
