<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version='2.0' xmlns:atom='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom'>
<channel>
<title>Nompower</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/</link>
<description>Daily digest</description>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 11:11:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
<item>
<title>Hyundai testing humanoid robots at US plants amid Korean union warnings</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-hyundai-testing-humanoid-robots-at-us-plants-amid-korean-union-warnings.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-hyundai-testing-humanoid-robots-at-us-plants-amid-korean-union-warnings.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 11:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
<description>The factory floor of the future is starting to look a lot more like a sci-fi movie set, and Hyundai is rolling the cameras. The automotive giant is reportedly moving beyond robotic arms and beginning real-world tests of full-fledged humanoi</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Quantization-Aware Distillation for NVFP4 Inference Accuracy Recovery</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-quantization-aware-distillation-for-nvfp4-inference-accuracy-recovery.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-quantization-aware-distillation-for-nvfp4-inference-accuracy-recovery.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 10:12:26 +0000</pubDate>
<description>Hold onto your GPUs, because the race to cram ever-larger AI brains into ever-tighter memory budgets just got a major new weapon. A quiet but potentially seismic shift in model optimization is emerging, promising to make the most aggressive</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Next-generation AI &#x27;swarms&#x27; will invade social media by mimicking human behavior and harassing real users, researchers warn</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-next-generation-ai-swarms-will-invade-social-media-by-mimicking-human-behavior-a.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-next-generation-ai-swarms-will-invade-social-media-by-mimicking-human-behavior-a.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
<description>Imagine logging into your favorite social media app, only to find your feed swarmed by eerily persuasive, coordinated accounts that argue, agree, and amplify messages with superhuman speed and stamina. This isn&#x27;t a scene from a sci-fi thril</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Google disrupts IPIDEA residential proxy networks fueled by malware</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-google-disrupts-ipidea-residential-proxy-networks-fueled-by-malware.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-google-disrupts-ipidea-residential-proxy-networks-fueled-by-malware.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 08:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
<description>In a digital game of whack-a-mole, one of the biggest hammers just came down. Google has taken a significant swing at the shadowy infrastructure that turns infected personal computers into a global, for-hire proxy service, directly targetin</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Microsoft to disable NTLM by default in future Windows releases</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-microsoft-to-disable-ntlm-by-default-in-future-windows-releases.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-microsoft-to-disable-ntlm-by-default-in-future-windows-releases.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 07:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
<description>Get ready to say a final, long-overdue goodbye to a digital dinosaur. Microsoft is reportedly pulling the plug on one of Windows&#x27; oldest and most vulnerable security protocols, signaling a major shift in how our machines will talk to each o</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Instagram might soon let you remove yourself from someone’s Close Friends list</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-instagram-might-soon-let-you-remove-yourself-from-someones-close-friends-list.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-instagram-might-soon-let-you-remove-yourself-from-someones-close-friends-list.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
<description>Get ready for a potential power shift in the delicate dance of social media intimacy. A new discovery within Instagram&#x27;s code suggests the platform is testing a feature that could finally give you a say in who gets to see your most private </description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Oracle seeks to build bridges with MySQL developers</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-oracle-seeks-to-build-bridges-with-mysql-developers.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-oracle-seeks-to-build-bridges-with-mysql-developers.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 05:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
<description>In a move that has the developer world doing a collective double-take, database behemoth Oracle appears to be extending an olive branch to the very community that has often viewed it with deep suspicion: the open-source MySQL faithful. The </description>
</item>
<item>
<title>ICE Is Using a Terrifying Palantir App to Determine Where to Raid</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-ice-is-using-a-terrifying-palantir-app-to-determine-where-to-raid.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-ice-is-using-a-terrifying-palantir-app-to-determine-where-to-raid.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
<description>In the shadows of immigration enforcement, a powerful new tool is reportedly guiding the hand of the state, powered not by boots on the ground, but by predictive algorithms and vast data troves. The Alleged &quot;FALCON&quot; System in Action Accordi</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Jeffrey Epstein emails claim Bill Gates hid STD from wife after sex with ‘Russian girls’</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-jeffrey-epstein-emails-claim-bill-gates-hid-std-from-wife-after-sex-with-russian.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-jeffrey-epstein-emails-claim-bill-gates-hid-std-from-wife-after-sex-with-russian.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 03:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
<description>Just when you thought the sprawling saga of Jeffrey Epstein couldn&#x27;t possibly intersect with another corner of the tech world, a new cache of alleged emails throws a jarring, unverified accusation directly into the orbit of one of its most </description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Nvidia&#x27;s plan to invest up to $100 billion in OpenAI has stalled, WSJ reports</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-nvidia-s-plan-to-invest-up-to-100-billion-in-openai-has-stalled-wsj-reports.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-nvidia-s-plan-to-invest-up-to-100-billion-in-openai-has-stalled-wsj-reports.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 00:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
<description>In a move that could reshape the entire trajectory of the AI arms race, a blockbuster deal between two of the industry&#x27;s titans appears to have hit a major roadblock. The Stalled $100 Billion Gambit According to a report from The Wall Stree</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
