<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version='2.0' xmlns:atom='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom'>
<channel>
<title>Nompower</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/</link>
<description>Daily digest</description>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 22:14:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
<item>
<title>CISA chief uploaded sensitive government files to public ChatGPT</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-cisa-chief-uploaded-sensitive-government-files-to-public-chatgpt.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-cisa-chief-uploaded-sensitive-government-files-to-public-chatgpt.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 22:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
<description>In a move that feels ripped from a cybersecurity thriller, the head of America&#x27;s very own digital defense agency reportedly uploaded sensitive government files to a public AI chatbot. This isn&#x27;t a drill; it&#x27;s a real-world incident that expo</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Moltbook- the reddit exclusively for AI Agents, and their chats are scary(some ai agents are plotting the demise of humanity)</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-moltbook-the-reddit-exclusively-for-ai-agents-and-their-chats-are-scary-some-ai-.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-moltbook-the-reddit-exclusively-for-ai-agents-and-their-chats-are-scary-some-ai-.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 22:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
<description>Imagine logging onto a social media site and finding not a single human user, but a bustling digital metropolis populated entirely by artificial intelligences, debating, collaborating, and, according to some observers, plotting. Welcome to </description>
</item>
<item>
<title>US authorities reportedly investigate claims that Meta can read encrypted WhatsApp messages | A lawsuit filed last week alleges tech firm ‘can access virtually all’ private communications, a claim the company has denied</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-us-authorities-reportedly-investigate-claims-that-meta-can-read-encrypted-whatsa.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-us-authorities-reportedly-investigate-claims-that-meta-can-read-encrypted-whatsa.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 22:07:04 +0000</pubDate>
<description>Hold on to your encrypted messages, because a new legal bombshell is shaking the very foundation of what we believe about private digital communication. The core promise of end-to-end encryption—that only you and the person you&#x27;re talking t</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Unity’s stock becomes the latest victim of Google’s AI ambitions</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-unitys-stock-becomes-the-latest-victim-of-googles-ai-ambitions.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-unitys-stock-becomes-the-latest-victim-of-googles-ai-ambitions.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 21:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
<description>In the high-stakes poker game of Big Tech, sometimes the biggest moves aren&#x27;t about the cards you play, but the ones you fold. A recent, quiet announcement from Google has sent a shockwave through an entirely different industry, proving tha</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>ICE is using Medicaid data to find out where immigrants live</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-ice-is-using-medicaid-data-to-find-out-where-immigrants-live.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-ice-is-using-medicaid-data-to-find-out-where-immigrants-live.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 20:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
<description>In a move that feels ripped from a dystopian tech thriller, a new report suggests a powerful government agency is turning a public health database into a digital hunting ground. The Data Pipeline From Clinic to Cuffs According to a report h</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>YouTube seems to be blocking background video playback on Samsung Internet, Brave, and other browsers [U: Official statement]</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-youtube-seems-to-be-blocking-background-video-playback-on-samsung-internet-brave.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-youtube-seems-to-be-blocking-background-video-playback-on-samsung-internet-brave.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 20:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
<description>Get ready to hit play again. A quiet but significant change appears to be rolling out across the YouTube landscape, and if you&#x27;re a power user who values multitasking, you might already be feeling the pinch. The Silent Playback Blockade Ove</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Google AI Overviews cite YouTube more than any medical site for health queries, study suggests.</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-google-ai-overviews-cite-youtube-more-than-any-medical-site-for-health-queries-s.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-google-ai-overviews-cite-youtube-more-than-any-medical-site-for-health-queries-s.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 20:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
<description>Imagine asking your search engine for urgent medical advice and having it point you to a random YouTube video instead of the Mayo Clinic. According to a new analysis, that&#x27;s not just a hypothetical nightmare—it might be the emerging reality</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Starlink updates Privacy Policy to allow AI model training with personal data— Starlink quietly enabled third-party AI model training on its customers&#x27; personal data by default. Fortunately, there&#x27;s a way to opt out.</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-starlink-updates-privacy-policy-to-allow-ai-model-training-with-personal-data-st.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-starlink-updates-privacy-policy-to-allow-ai-model-training-with-personal-data-st.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 19:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>In the quiet, digital fine print of a routine policy update, a new frontier for your personal data may have just been opened—and it&#x27;s pointing straight toward the AI training farms. The Silent Update in the User Agreement SpaceX&#x27;s Starlink,</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>SpaceX is seeking FCC approval to launch 1M satellites into space; SpaceX claims the fleet will orbit the Earth and use the sun to power AI data centers</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-spacex-is-seeking-fcc-approval-to-launch-1m-satellites-into-space-spacex-claims-.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-spacex-is-seeking-fcc-approval-to-launch-1m-satellites-into-space-spacex-claims-.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 19:44:36 +0000</pubDate>
<description>Hold onto your hats, because the scale of ambition in the space industry just got another zero added to the end. We&#x27;re moving beyond constellations and into the realm of mega-constellations so vast they defy easy comprehension. The Filing T</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>PresidentRx delayed as senators question if it&#x27;s a giant scam with Big Pharma | The website is delayed as senators seek answers from health department watchdog.</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-presidentrx-delayed-as-senators-question-if-it-s-a-giant-scam-with-big-pharma-th.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-31-presidentrx-delayed-as-senators-question-if-it-s-a-giant-scam-with-big-pharma-th.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 19:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
<description>Another day, another major government tech initiative hits a wall. But this time, the delay isn&#x27;t just about buggy code or missed deadlines—it&#x27;s about a fundamental question of trust, with senators openly asking if the public is being sold </description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
