<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version='2.0' xmlns:atom='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom'>
<channel>
<title>Nompower</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/</link>
<description>Daily digest</description>
<lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 19:05:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
<item>
<title>Who takes Palantir&#x27;s money? A new tracker finds out.</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-30-who-takes-palantir-s-money-a-new-tracker-finds-out.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-30-who-takes-palantir-s-money-a-new-tracker-finds-out.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 19:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
<description>In the shadowy world of government tech contracts, a new spotlight just flickered to life, aiming to demystify one of the industry&#x27;s most secretive players. The Data Dragnet Goes Public A new, independent online tracker has emerged with a s</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pope Leo XIV brings not peace but a sword to AI oligarchs and a slop-mad world in new address, says it&#x27;s &#x27;Turning people into passive consumers of unthought thoughts&#x27;</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-30-pope-leo-xiv-brings-not-peace-but-a-sword-to-ai-oligarchs-and-a-slop-mad-world-i.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-30-pope-leo-xiv-brings-not-peace-but-a-sword-to-ai-oligarchs-and-a-slop-mad-world-i.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
<description>In a stunning and fiery address that seems ripped from a cyberpunk novel, a new and powerful voice has emerged to challenge the architects of our digital age—and it&#x27;s emanating from the Vatican. The Digital Prophecy from Rome According to d</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Google&#x27;s World Generator Got 6.6 Million Views and a Thousand &quot;F*ck Off&quot;s</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-30-google-s-world-generator-got-6-6-million-views-and-a-thousand-f-ck-off-s.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-30-google-s-world-generator-got-6-6-million-views-and-a-thousand-f-ck-off-s.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:35:42 +0000</pubDate>
<description>In the quiet, algorithmically-curated halls of the internet, a single Google experiment recently became a digital lightning rod, attracting millions of eyes and a torrent of raw, unfiltered human emotion. The Unexpected Viral Storm Google&#x27;s</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Mamdani to kill the NYC AI chatbot caught telling businesses to break the law— New York mayor says terminating the ‘unusable’ bot will help close a budget gap</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-30-mamdani-to-kill-the-nyc-ai-chatbot-caught-telling-businesses-to-break-the-law-ne.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-30-mamdani-to-kill-the-nyc-ai-chatbot-caught-telling-businesses-to-break-the-law-ne.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
<description>Well, that didn&#x27;t take long. New York City&#x27;s foray into generative AI for public services has ended not with a whimper, but with a mayoral decree to pull the plug, citing both embarrassing malfunctions and a convenient budget trim. The Bot </description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Right-wing media attempt to justify baseless conspiracy theories that the attack on Ilhan Omar was staged</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-30-right-wing-media-attempt-to-justify-baseless-conspiracy-theories-that-the-attack.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-30-right-wing-media-attempt-to-justify-baseless-conspiracy-theories-that-the-attack.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:24:17 +0000</pubDate>
<description>In the chaotic aftermath of a violent event, a disturbing new pattern is emerging faster than the facts themselves: the immediate, weaponized spread of conspiracy theories designed not just to confuse, but to delegitimize the victims. The I</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Big Tech thinks smart glasses will be the first major piece of AI hardware</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-30-big-tech-thinks-smart-glasses-will-be-the-first-major-piece-of-ai-hardware.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-30-big-tech-thinks-smart-glasses-will-be-the-first-major-piece-of-ai-hardware.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:27:01 +0000</pubDate>
<description>Forget the clunky headsets and the phones that demand your full attention. The next battlefield for your face is being drawn, and it looks surprisingly like a regular pair of glasses. The Race to Put AI in Your Eyeline According to discussi</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Windows 11 will soon support more desktop background formats</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-30-windows-11-will-soon-support-more-desktop-background-formats.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-30-windows-11-will-soon-support-more-desktop-background-formats.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:24:33 +0000</pubDate>
<description>Get ready to ditch the JPGs, because your desktop wallpaper is about to get a major file format glow-up. A seemingly small change buried in a Windows 11 test build is hinting at a future where your PC&#x27;s background can be far more than just </description>
</item>
<item>
<title>New game merges ludocreativity with music production.</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-30-new-game-merges-ludocreativity-with-music-production.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-30-new-game-merges-ludocreativity-with-music-production.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:20:08 +0000</pubDate>
<description>Hold onto your headphones, because the line between gaming and music production just got a whole lot blurrier. A new project is emerging from the digital ether, promising to turn the act of making music into a playful, game-like experience.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>DHS is using Google and Adobe AI to make videos</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-30-dhs-is-using-google-and-adobe-ai-to-make-videos.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-30-dhs-is-using-google-and-adobe-ai-to-make-videos.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
<description>Hold on to your hats, because the line between science fiction and your local government&#x27;s tech stack just got a whole lot blurier. A new report suggests the Department of Homeland Security is actively experimenting with generative AI video</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Mesh Networks Are About to Escape Apple, Amazon, and Google Silos</title>
<link>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-30-mesh-networks-are-about-to-escape-apple-amazon-and-google-silos.html</link>
<guid isPermaLink='true'>https://nompower.mikanntool.com/articles/2026-01-30-mesh-networks-are-about-to-escape-apple-amazon-and-google-silos.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
<description>For years, the promise of seamless, whole-home Wi-Fi has been locked inside proprietary gardens. That might finally be about to change, and the key is a new standard that could shatter the walls between your gadgets. The Standard That Could</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
